Hi there and welcome to the Data Analyst Nanodegree Program.
你好 欢迎来到数据分析纳米学位！
I'm Mike and I'm one of the instructors for this nanodegree program.
我是这门课程的讲师之一 我的名字是 Mike
More and more companies all over the world are gathering
当今世界 越来越多的公司正在执行数据策略
tons of data to help them make informed business decisions.
依赖数据来做出正确的业务决策
However, the data on its own isn't useful,
数据本身是不具有任何意义的
they also need employees who can make sense of it.
它们需要经过数据分析师的处理和解析才会有意义
That's why data analyst and data scientist are consistently
这就是为什么在当今的就业市场上 数据分析师和数据科学家一直都是
some of the most in-demand jobs today especially in the tech world.
最热门的岗位之一
The goal of this program is to help you develop all of the skills you
本课程的主要目的就是培养你的数据科学技能
need to start or advance your career as a data analyst.
为你的数据分析师职业打下坚实的基础
Not only that, you will also gain
同时 你也将了解和学习一些基本技能和知识 它们不仅在数据科学领域
the fundamental skills and knowledge necessary for work in data science,
在机器学习和人工智能领域
machine learning and artificial intelligence.
也是非常重要的基础
This program has been built 3for students with some experience working with data.
本门课程适合有数据基础的学员
If you've run basic queries in SQL and know how to write function in Python,
如果你会用 SQL 执行基本查询 会用 Python 写函数
you're ready to start.
那么 你就可以开始学习啦
In this program, we will focus on Python which is
本课的一大重点是 Python
quickly becoming the most popular programming language for working with data.
Python 近年来益发地成为处理数据时应用最广泛的编程语言
First, you'll cover the major Python frameworks you'll be using for
首先 你会学习用于数据分析的两个主要的 Python 工具
most of your data analysis, NumPy and Pandas.
NumPy 和 Pandas
Next, you will use statistics to make decisions based on data.
然后 你将学习统计学知识
You will then see how to gather,
同时 了解怎样收集、评估、清理数据
assess and clean data,
这些都是数据清洗的基本流程
Finally, you'll learn how to effectively explore your data and share your findings by
最后 你会学习如何有效地进行数据探索 用 Python matplotlib 和 seaborn 来创建可视化
building visualizations using Python's matplotlib and seaborn libraries.
同时将你的数据洞察通过可视化传达给别人
When you complete this program,
从本课毕业就意味着你拥有了
you'll graduate ready to get a job as
数据分析师应该具备的基本技能
a data analyst or to continue your journey in the world of data.
这些技能会支撑你在数据行业的继续探索
So let's get started.
接下来 就可以学习吧！